想在此处添加您的广告信息？立即联系 www.OpenSubtitles.org
彼得的龙
翻托邦字幕组
原创译制
微博 weibo.com/fantopia
翻译&压制&特效&校对
Yatamisaki
FANTOPIA
翻托邦字幕组
扫码关注翻托邦
字幕组微博，获
取更多影视资源
资讯
翻托邦字幕组长
期招募英\日翻
译及后期，详情
请见微博置顶
流行病学常用术语 泛指对象接触过某种欲研究的因素 具有某种特征或行为
BGM:Go North(Dragon song redux) - Traditiona music
BGM:Nobody Knows - The Lumineers
BGM:So long, Marianne - Leonard Cohen
BGM:It's A Good Day - Peggy Lee
BGM:Something on your mind - St.Vincent
BGM:Something wild - Lindsey Stirling featuring Andrew McMahon In The Wilderness
BGM:Go North(Dragon song redux) - Traditiona music
欢迎来到米尔黑文
塔沃特峡谷
埃利奥特迷路了
杰克
我们去抓龙了
嘉文
"这是...
"This is...
一个小狗的故事
the story of a puppy.
他的名字叫...
His name is...
埃..."
El-I..."
- 埃利奥特 - "埃利奥特"
- Elliot. - "Elliot".
"他的名字叫埃利奥特"
"His name is Elliot."
你会读了
You got it.
"他要进行一场
"He is going on an...
冒险..."
adventure..."
- 一场冒险 - 什么意思
- An adventure. - What's that?
一场冒险
An adventure?
你不知道冒险什么意思吗
You don't know what an adventure is?
我们现在就在冒险
What we're on right now.
在荒郊野外
Out here in the wild,
方圆百里一个人都没有...
not another soul in sight for hundreds of miles...
只有星星在指引我们
with just the stars to guide us.
冒险很可怕吗
Is it scary?
那是关于冒险的另一面
That's the other thing about adventures.
你得勇敢一点
You gotta be brave.
你勇敢吗
Are you brave?
你当然勇敢
Of course you are.
你是我见过最勇敢的男孩
I think you are the bravest boy I've ever met.
妈妈
Momma.
你要吃了我吗
Are you gonna eat me?
# 去北方 用你脚上的翅膀去北方 #
Go North, go North with wings on your feet.
# 乘着风去北方 那里有三条交汇的河 #
Go North with the wind where the three rivers meet
# 在树林之中 有一块空地 #
There's a clearing of sorts in the circle of trees
# 野外的天空闪烁星座点点 #
Where the wild constellations shine one two and three
# 看看你的周围 #
Look all around you and see
# 森林的深处有古龙 #
Deep in the forest there dragons will be
只要人们
As long as people have been
进入这片森林...
going into these woods...
就一直有米尔黑文之龙的传说流传出来
there have been stories about the Millhaven dragon.
那首歌怎么唱的来着
How does that song go again?
他们来自北方 对吧
They come from the North, right?
在高高的山上
Way up there in the mountains
人迹罕见之境
where few people have ever been.
但有时候
But sometimes,
龙也会迷路
a dragon gets lost from its family...
飞到离家很远很远的地方
and winds up very, very far from home.
传说 它住在这片森林里
They say it lives in these very woods.
夜里你能听到它的咆哮
That you can hear its roar at night.
左一个传言 右一个谣言 但据我所知...
They say this, they say that, but, as far as I know...
没有人真正见过这只龙
not one soul has ever actually seen this dragon.
除了我
Except me.
你见过一只龙
You saw a dragon?
没错
I sure did.
千真万确
它长什么样
What'd it look like?
绿色的
Well, it was green.
浑身都是绿色
Green all over.
除了他的眼睛
Except for his eyes.
他的眼睛是红的 就像地狱之火
His eyes were red. Like hellfire.
我都来不及眨眼...
Before I could even blink...
它就抬起头 张开它有力的下颚...
it rears back its head, opens its mighty jaw...
然后喷火...
and shoots out...
于是我当机立断
So, I wasn't gonna waste my breath.
翻滚到一旁 跌跌撞撞地站起来...
I rolled out the way, scrambled to my feet...
准备迎接一场战斗
ready for the fight that was gonna come.
但当我举起来复枪...
But as I raised my rifle...
那只龙用它的爪子向我扑来
the dragon comes at me with one swipe of its claw...
把枪从我的手里打飞
knocks the gun right out of my hands.
怎么办
Now, what?
情况不太妙啊
Things are really not looking good here.
但我还没有完蛋 还不是时候
But I wasn't gonna be done. Not yet.
我拿出我的小折刀...
I just took out my pocket knife...
一旦龙动我一下...
And as the dragon set upon me...
就送他回家
I drove it home.
又在唬小孩了 爸爸
Scaring the kids again, Dad?
不不不 我只是在帮助他们...
No, no, no. I was just giving them a leg up...
了解那片森林里有什么
on what's out there in those woods.
我每天都去那片森林
Well, I'm out in those woods every day...
我见过熊和山猫
and while I have seen bears and bobcats...
以及你们能想到的各种鸟类
and just about every type of bird you can imagine.
从没见过龙
I have never seen a dragon.
你没见过
Just because you don't see something,
不代表没有
doesn't mean it's not there.
你说那是真的
And just because you say it's true,
不代表就是真的
doesn't mean it is.
可是 我现在就要过去
But, I'm headed out there right now.
回头告诉你们 我有没有看见
I'll let you all know if I see anything
巨大的 绿色的 喷火的东西
big and green and breathing fire.
米查姆先生 我相信你
Mr. Meacham, I believe you.
很高兴你相信我 看看我的女儿...
Well, I'm glad you do. See, my daughter...
她见多识广
she knows a thing or two
但只了解她见过的东西
but only if it's staring at her in the face.
如果你的生活
If you go through life
只经历一些眼前的事情...
only seeing what's right in front of you...
你就会错过很多
you're gonna miss out on a whole lot.
看 在这一点上 你们已经有优势了
See, and that's where you guys have the upper hand.
记住我的话...
Because mark my words...
龙还在森林里
that dragon is still out there.
如果你们去了那片森林
And if you were to go out there to those woods...
去到没人去的地方...
where no one ever goes...
就能找到他
then you might find him.
除非 他先找到你
Unless, he found you first.
抓住你了
Gotcha!
嘿 埃利奥特
Hey, Elliot!
这是干什么
What was that for?
快来 埃利奥特
Come on, Elliot!
埃利奥特
Elliot?
Elliot!
快来
Come on!
再高点
Higher!
你在看什么
What are you looking at?
这边吗
This way?
我们离家很远了
We're pretty far from home.
你在这啊
There you are.
没人会把你砍倒了
No one's gonna cut you down now.
你要走了吗 格蕾丝
You ready to go, Grace?
没错
Yeah.
再等一会儿
Just a second.
拜托 格蕾丝 别再这样
Come on, Grace. Not again.
我就是报复一下
I'm just settling a score.
一次为了杰克 一次为了自己 对吧
One for Jack. One for you, huh?
没错 差不多吧
Yeah. Something like that.
你们两个不是结婚了吗
Aren't you two supposed to be getting hitched?
没错 就是让他保持警惕而已
Yep! Just keeping him on his toes.
看
Look.
埃利奥特
Elliot!
彼得和埃利奥特...
Pete and Elliot...
要...
are going...
然后...
And then...
他们下降 下降 下降
Then they go down, and down, and down!
然后...
And then...
我想知道那位女士从哪来
I wonder where that lady came from.
别担心
Don't worry.
我不会让她伤害你
I won't let her hurt you.
晚安 埃利奥特
Good night, Elliot.
埃利奥特
Elliot.
树倒啦
Timber!
嘿 嘉文
Hey, Gavin.
都砍到森林深处了 杰克没意见吗
Did Jack give the okay to cut this deep?
别管杰克 继续砍
Don't worry about Jack. Just keep cutting.
谁同意的砍这里的树的
Who said it was okay to be here?
我只是按他们说的做
I just go where they tell me.
杰克去哪了
Where's Jack?
他在那
There he is!
这也太出格了 杰克
This is so out of line, Jack.
你们不该砍到这深处附近的
You're not supposed to be cutting anywhere near this deep.
我对此一无所知
I didn't know anything about this either.
这不是我下的命令 格蕾丝
This wasn't my call, Grace.
那是谁的命令
Then, whose was it?
怪不得
Of course.
让我来处理 好吗
Let me handle this, please?
问题是 你不会处理的
You don't handle it. That's the problem.
你说得对 嘉文个性如此
You're right, and Gavin is Gavin.
他是我的兄弟
He's my brother.
嘿 我要去学校了
Hey, I have to get to school.
你能在卡车里等吗 亲爱的
Could you wait in the truck, sweetheart?
我们一会儿就好
We'll just be a minute.
我们来看看地图
Let's go through the maps.
再看一遍
Let's review them.
你好
Hello?
等等
Wait!
你在哪
Where are you?
你怎么上去的
How'd you get up there?
拜托 慢一点
Come on! Slow down.
你真会爬树
You're pretty good at this.
救命
Help!
别放手
Don't let go!
不
No!
别碰
Don't!
我受伤了
I'm hurt!
你几岁了
How old are you?
五岁
Five?
那你可长得真高
You're pretty big to be a five-year-old.
你叫什么
What's your name?
彼得
Pete.
看来你确实叫彼得
You look like a Pete.
- 我叫娜塔莉 - 娜塔莉
- My name's Natalie. - Natalie!
- 爸爸 - 娜塔莉
- Daddy! - Natalie!
爸爸
Daddy!
你在想什么 你不能这么跑出来
What were you thinking? You can't run away like that.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我从树上摔下来了
I fell out of a tree.
你从树上摔下来了
You fell out of a tree?
你在树上干嘛
What were you doing in a tree?
跟着他
Following him.
他叫彼得
His name is Pete.
嘿
Hey.
彼得 是你的名字吗
Pete? Is that your name?
彼得
Pete?
等等
Wait, wait, wait!
你来自哪里
Where'd you come from?
你的父母去哪了
Do you know where your parents are?
你的家人呢
Your family?
嘿
Hey.
你从哪得到那个的
Where'd you get that?
等等
Wait!
- 埃利奥特 - 彼得
- Elliot! - Pete!
这里 小家伙
Whoa, there, little buddy.
你要去哪啊 这么...
Where are you going so...
嘿 孩子 回来
Hey, kid! Come back here.
过来 孩子
Come on, kid!
小心 嘉文
Careful, Gavin!
没关系
Doesn't matter.
警长 游骑兵 所有人
The sheriff, the rangers, everybody else
都会封闭这个地方...
are gonna be locking this site down...
直到找出这个孩子从哪来的
until they figure out where that kid came from.
嘿 你听到了吗
Hey, you hear that?
别转移话题 嘉文
Don't change the subject, Gavin.
每一次 我想采取一些主动...
Every time I try and take some initiative...
你就让我闭嘴
you shut me down.
如果我们没有砍到这里...
If we hadn't been cutting out here...
就不能及时发现这个孩子
we never would've found that kid in the first place.
我们在这做好事 杰克
We're doing good work here, Jack.
我们需要一批好木材 才有竞争力
And we need a big score to help us compete.
那几年之后...
What about a few years from now...
因为你提前动工
when we have nothing left to cut down
我们无树可砍怎么办
because you keep jumping the gun?
- 你要去哪 - 你觉得呢
- Where are you going? - Where do you think?
你不是唯一一个我操心的家人
You're not the only family I gotta worry about.
让我知道彼得的情况 好吗
Let me know how Pete's doing, will ya?
怎么了 嘉文 杰克训了你一顿吗
What's wrong, Gavin? Jack giving you a hard time?
你知道杰克这个人
Oh, you know Jack.
因为被女朋友骂了一顿 他很恼火
He's just sore because his girlfriend's stepping on his toes.
那是个红头发美妞啊 伙计
Redheads, man.
- 小心 - 小心
- Look out! - Look out!
那是什么
What was that?
我们去打猎
Let's go hunting.
彼得
Pete.
该醒醒了 彼得
Time to wake up, Pete.
妈妈
Momma?
埃利奥特
Elliot?
他怎么样了
How's he doing?
总而言之 很好
Pretty well, all things considered.
没有营养不良或者严重的暴露迹象
No signs of malnourishment or serious exposure.
头部应该有撞击 但...
He might have a bump to the head, but...
- 幸运的孩子 - 非常幸运
- Lucky kid. - Super lucky.
他怎么会在那里
How'd he get out there?
他可能曾在那野餐或者野营
My guess, he was on a picnic or a camping trip.
和他家人走散了
He wandered off from his family,
迷路了
got himself lost.
当然 但什么时候
Sure, but when?
看起来他在外面
It looks like he's been out there
待了不知道多久
for who knows how long.
他有这个
And he had this.
你确定是你的吗
You sure that's yours?
非常确定
Pretty sure.
我们来了 都打理好了
Here we are. All fixed up.
过来 感觉如何
Hey, there. How you feeling?
就是擦伤而已 彼得在哪
It was just a scrape. Where's Pete?
我要带娜塔莉回家
I'm gonna take Natalie home,
然后再回森林
then head back out to the forest.
也许那里有...
Maybe there's something out there...
一些线索之类的
some clue, or something.
他醒了能叫我吗
Could you call me when he wakes up?
当然
Of course.
当他醒了
When he wakes up,
我认为最好一切都慢慢来
I think it would be best to take things slowly.
一步一步来 让他知道自己安全
One step at a time. Let him know he's safe.
我们不知道他经历了什么
We don't know what he's been through.
我们给社会服务部门打了电话
We put in a call in to Social Services.
他们知道怎么处理这种事
They'll know exactly how to handle this.
目前 这里会照顾好他
For the time being, he'll be just fine right here.
其实 他不见了
Actually, he's gone.
- 谁不见了 亲爱的 - 彼得
- Who's gone, sweetheart? - Pete.
埃利奥特
Elliot!
# 没人知道如何说再见 #
Nobody knows how to say goodbye
# 直到你尝试 感觉很简单 #
It seems so easy till you try
# 而那些瞬间 #
Then the moments
# 与你擦身而过 #
Pass you by
# 没人知道如何说再见 #
Nobody knows how to say goodbye
- 天哪 - 梅西 闭嘴
- Oh, my goodness! - Macy, stop!
别对着狗吼
Don't you bark at our dog!
# 穿过黑夜 来到黎明 #
Through the darkness to the dawn
孩子 停下
Kid, stop!
等等
Wait, wait!
该死 站在那别动
Damn it! Stop right there.
我找到他了 他在路口 就在主路和...
I've got him. He's on the corner of Main and...
他曾在路口...
He was on the corner of...
我跟丢了
I've lost him.
嘿 看啊
Hey, look.
# 爱是深沉的 #
Love is deep
# 路是漫长的 #
This road is long
# 我坚持不停地跑 #
It moves my feet to carry on
# 当你走失 我很伤心 #
Beats my heart When you are gone
# 爱是深沉的 路是漫长的 #
Love is deep, This road is long
嘿 坐下
Hey, sit down!
帅呆了
Awesome!
# 没人知道故事如何结束 #
Nobody knows how the story ends
彼得
Pete!
没事的
It's okay.
我们不会伤害你
We're not gonna hurt you.
我保证 好吗
I promise. All right?
过来
Come here.
静下来 静下来
Hold on. Hold on.
没事的 静下来 静下来
It's okay. Hold on. Hold on.
深呼吸 深呼吸 深呼吸
Breathe. Breathe. Breathe.
嘿 伙计们 过来看看
Hey, guys! Come check this out.
嘿
Hey.
脚印很新
Fresh.
一天都不到
Not even a day old.
你怎么看
What do you think?
一头熊
A bear?
你们见过这么大的熊
You ever seen a bear that big?
我见过一次
Thought I did once.
明显是博比的姐姐
Turns out it was just Bobby's sister.
好吧 让我抓点兔子
All right, let's catch me some rabbits.
今晚我会带他回家
I'll bring him home tonight.
好的 非常感谢 警长
Okay, thank you so much, Sheriff.
- 你自己小心 - 谢谢
- You take care of yourself. - Thank you.
再见
Bye.
记住 有什么问题 我都在
Remember, any problems... I'm the guy.
好的
Will do.
嘿 彼得
Hey, Pete.
别担心 你不用回医院了
Don't worry, you don't have to go back to the hospital.
我们去我家
We're going to my house.
今天阳光灿烂
Plenty of sunshine through today,
有季节性的...
with seasonal...
# 我曾常以为自己是流浪男孩 #
I used to think I was some kind of gypsy boy
# 在我让你带我回家之前 #
Before I let you take me home
# 再见 玛丽安 #
Now so long, Marianne
# 是时候我们开始再次 #
It's time that we began
# 对所有的一切  #
To laugh and cry and cry
# 大笑 痛哭 痛哭 大笑 #
And laugh about it all again
好了 我们到了
Okay. Here we are.
需要帮助吗
Need a little help?
- 彼得 不 等等 - 等等
- Pete, no! Wait! - Wait!
等等 等等
Wait! Wait, wait.
你跑得真快
You are fast.
天哪
Oh, my goodness.
怎么了 亲爱的
What's wrong, honey?
你饿了吗
Are you hungry?
我们进去吧 吃点东西
Let's go inside. Let's go get something to eat.
我想回家
I want to go home.
我知道
I know.
你家在哪 能告诉我吗
Where is your home? Can you tell me?
这样吧
How about this?
如果你现在和我进去
If you come inside with me now,
那明天...
then tomorrow...
我就带你回森林
I'll take you back out to the woods
你就能告诉我 你住在哪
and you can show me exactly where you live.
怎么样
How does that sound?
当我还是个小女孩时
You know, when I was a little girl...
我特别想住在森林里
I wanted to live in the forest more than anything.
我喜欢待在外面
I loved being out there.
和松鼠啊 小鸟啊
It was so fun with the squirrels
树啊待在一起 太有趣了
and the birds and the trees.
所以 当我长大了...
So, when I grew up...
就把这作为我的工作 保护森林
I made it my job to protect the woods
和里面的一切
and everything in them.
可能还包括你
Which I suppose includes you.
和埃利奥特吗
And Elliot?
埃利奥特是谁
Who's Elliot?
格蕾丝
Grace?
你确定要留他吗
Are you sure about this?
找到他的家就好了
It's just until we found out where he belongs.
谁知道呢
Who knows?
也许和他同龄的人能让他敞开心扉
Maybe being around someone his own age will help him open up.
也许能说出他从哪来的
Maybe he'll tell us where he came from.
你别碰它 要吃它
You don't touch it. You eat it.
像这样
Like this.
我得承认...
I gotta admit...
住在森林里 特立独行...
living out in the woods, doing things his own way...
听起来像是男版的你啊
sounds like a boy after your own heart.
我们可能迷路了
I think we're lost.
嘉文知道他在做什么
Ah, Gavin knows what he's doing.
你三英里前就这么说
You said that three miles ago.
拐弯后 河就向上了
The river's up around that bend.
我们跟着走就行了
We can just follow that,
就能返回起点
and we'll be back where we started.
那样河就向下了
The river's back that way.
我们一直在绕圈圈
We've been going in circles.
我以前从没走过这么远
I've never been out this far before.
你知道我们在哪吗
Do you know where we are?
看看这个
Look at this.
到底是什么
What on Earth?
你得来看看
You've got to see this.
你觉得是那个孩子干的吗
You think that kid did all this?
一个孩子怎么能做成这样
What would a kid be doing this far out?
嘿 伙计们 看看这个
Hey, guys! Look at this.
快跑
Run!
Hurry up!
快 快跑 跑
Come on! Faster! Run!
等等我
Wait for me!
快跑 起来 起来
Come on. Get up, get up!
发动卡车
Start the truck!
嘉文在哪
Where's Gavin?
快点 伙计
Come on, man!
等等
Wait!
快点 我们走
Come on, let's go!
快快快
Go, go, go!
什么鬼
What is that?
开车 伙计 快
Drive, man! Go!
嘉文 快走
Gavin, come on!
那是什么
What was that?
你看到了吗
Did you see that?
- 那是头怪兽 - 部 那是恶魔
- It was a monster! - No, man, that was a demon.
那是头怪兽恶魔
It was a monster demon.
那是只龙
It was a dragon!
把唱针放上去 然后...
You put the needle on, and...
# 没错 今天是个好日子 #
Yes, it's a good day
# 唱这首歌 #
For singing this song
# 今天是个好日子 #
And it's a good day
# 让它放吧 #
Let it play.
# 往前走 #
For moving along
# 没错 今天是个好日子 怎么出差错呢 #
Yes, it's a good day. How could anything go wrong?
那是我 那是我爸爸
That's me, and that's my dad.
那是他的兄弟
That's his brother.
这是格蕾丝 那是我的一家
There's Grace. That's my family.
家
Family.
我们就是一家
That's what we are.
# 梦想成真 没有损失 #
Everything to gain and nothing to lose
# 从早到晚的好日子 #
A good day from morning till night
把头放在这里 挪过去...
Put your head here, scooch down...
这是五岁
and now you're five years old.
# 如果你想表现良好 就要现在开始 #
You know you got to get going If you're gonna make a showin'
这是六岁 这是七岁
Now you're six, and now you're seven,
这是八岁 这是九岁...
now you're eight, now you're nine...
这是十岁
and now you're 10.
# 今天是治病的好日子 #
And it's a good day for curing your ills
# 所以深呼吸 丢了药片 #
So take a deep breath and throw away the pills
# 因为今天是从早到晚的好日子 #
'Cause it's a good day from morning till night
我曾到过这里 在东帕德
I was out here, at the Eastern Pad.
我记得 那是最后一次见到指南针
That's the last time I remember having my compass.
- 但那是... - 五十英里的东边
- But that's... - Fifty miles east.
离我们找到他的地方
From where we found him.
# 太阳 早上好 #
Good morning sun Good morning sun
# 今天照耀大地 #
Rise and shine today
# 如果你想表现良好 就要现在开始 #
You know you got to get going If you're gonna make a showin'
# 你就能得到优先权 #
And you got the right of way
我好久都没读过这本书了
I haven't read that book in forever.
我识字的时候 有人给了我这本书
Someone gave it to me when I was learning how to read.
没事的 小子
It's okay, buddy.
就是电话
It's just a phone.
# 今天是从早到晚的好日子 #
It's a good day from morning till night
# 从早到晚的好日子 #
Good day from morning till night
这是埃利奥特吗 彼得
Is this Elliot, Pete?
埃利奥特是个人吗
Is Elliot a person?
不
No.
他是什么呢
Well, what is he, then?
格蕾丝 是警长 他想和你说话
Grace, it's the Sheriff. He wants to talk to you.
喂
Hello?
嗨 格蕾丝 神秘小子怎么样
Hey, Grace. How's our mystery boy?
还是很神秘
Still a mystery.
有什么消息吗
Any news?
帕特查了失踪人口档案
Well, Pat went digging through our missing persons files.
他的身世追溯到了很远啊...
He had to go pretty far back...
但这不是好消息
but it's not good news.
可怜的彼得
Poor Pete.
我知道
I know.
我刚和社会服务部门通过电话
I just got off the phone with Social Services.
他们明天早上会得到他的抚养权
They're gonna take custody of him tomorrow morning.
彼得...
Pete...
埃利奥特是你想象的朋友吗
is Elliot your imaginary friend?
什么是想象
What's imaginary?
就是你脑中幻想的一个人
It's where you make someone up in your head...
这样你就有人说话了
so that you have someone to talk to.
能让你不这么孤单
It keeps you from being lonely.
他们有意思吗
Are they funny?
当然了
Sure.
他们会飞吗
Do they fly?
你想让他们做什么 他们就能做什么
I guess they can do whatever you want them to.
所以他们才是想象出来的
That's what makes them imaginary.
你也是我想象的朋友吗
Are you my imaginary friend, too?
我是真的
I'm real.
埃利奥特也是真的
So is Elliot.
干得好 小子
Good job, buddy.
妈妈 外面有个怪兽
Mommy, there's a monster outside.
我得回到他身边
I need to get back to him.
我走的时候 他很害怕
He gets scared when I'm gone.
他看起来像只龙
He looks like a dragon.
什么是龙
What's a dragon?
那就是龙
That's a dragon.
有一首歌
Like the song.
什么歌
What song?
我爸爸以前喜欢唱的歌
There's a song that my dad used to sing.
关于龙的 还有他们住在哪
It's about dragons and where they live.
# 去北方 用你脚上的翅膀去北方 #
Go North, Go North With wings on your feet
# 乘着风去北方 那里有三条交汇的河 #
Go North with the wind Where the three rivers meet
# 坐在最高的树旁 #
Now plant yourself down side the tallest tree
# 野外的天空闪烁星座点点 #
Measure the stars shining one two and three
# 看看你的周围 #
Look all around you and see
# 森林的深处有古龙 #
Deep in the forest there dragons will be
什么是北方
What's North?
是个方向
It's a direction.
要怎么去那
How do you get there?
你可以看看地图
You could look at a map.
或者跟着北极星
Or you could follow the North Star.
如果你跟着北极星一直走到最深处
If you follow it as far as you possibly can...
就能看到山
you get to the mountains.
那里就能找到他们
And that's where you'd find them.
我说的是龙
The dragons, I mean.
嘿
Hey.
我很久都没听过那首歌了
I haven't heard that song in forever.
娜塔莉 你能让
Natalie, do you think
我和彼得单独谈谈吗
I could talk to Pete alone for a moment?
好的
Okay.
回头见 彼得
See you in a minute, Pete.
嘿 过来
Hey, come here.
是你帮我找到的 对吧
You found this for me, didn't you?
那些树逃跑的地方
Where the trees ran away.
我十岁生日的时候 爸爸给了我这个
My dad gave this to me on my 10th birthday...
这样如果我迷路了
so that if I ever got lost,
就知道怎么回家
I'd know how to find my way back home.
彼得 亲爱的...
Pete, honey...
你还记得怎么进入森林的吗
do you remember how you got to the woods?
这是很久之前的事了 对吗
It was a long time ago, wasn't it?
我们当时在冒险
We were on an adventure.
你知道...
You know...
我和你差不多大的时候 失去了母亲
I lost my mom when I was not much older than you.
我知道有多艰难
I know how hard it can be.
但我希望你知道 你不孤单
But I want you to know, you are not alone.
我知道
I know.
是吗
You do?
我有埃利奥特
I have Elliot.
你能和我多说说埃利奥特吗
Can you tell me more about Elliot?
他是谁
Who is he?
他是我的朋友
He's my friend.
这是埃利奥特
This is Elliot?
他肯定是个很特别的朋友
He must be a very special friend.
他不喜欢人类 但他应该会喜欢你
He doesn't like most people. But I think he'd like you.
是吗
He would?
等着吧 明天
You'll see. Tomorrow.
明天
Tomorrow.
当我回家时
When I go home.
你会跟着我 对吗
You're coming with me, right?
当然
Of course.
你很勇敢
You're very brave.
你知道吗
Did you know that?
你是我见过最勇敢的男孩
You might be the bravest boy I've ever met.
- 嘉文 - 杰克
- Gavin? - Jack.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
你记得那些米查姆曾和我说的故事吗
You remember those stories that Meacham used to tell us?
和龙有关吗
About dragons?
不是他编的
He wasn't making them up.
我们发现了龙 还有一间树屋
We tracked it, and there was a treehouse.
我想开枪射它
I tried to shoot it,
但他把枪从我手里打飞了...
but it just ripped the gun right out of my hands...
还扭弯了枪 在它面前完全没用
and bent it like it was nothing.
嘉文 我不能因为
Gavin, I can't just head out
你觉得自己看见了龙
to the woods in the middle of the night...
大半夜的就去森林里
because you think you saw a dragon.
觉得我看见了 杰克 我知道自己看见了什么
Think I saw? Jack, I know what I saw.
没错
Yeah.
你不相信我
You don't believe me.
我告诉你 我们要做什么
I'll tell you what we'll do.
我们会打电话给林业部门
We'll call the Forestry,
告诉他们我们看见的
we tell them what you saw,
然后他们就会去处理的
and then they can go and deal with it.
好吧 我会拍到照片的
Fine. I get the picture.
我还指望家人呢
I thought I could count on family.
嘉文
Gavin.
别担心 明早见
Don't worry. See you in the morning.
"埃利奥特迷路了
"Elliot Gets Lost.
这是一个小狗的故事
This is the story of a little puppy.
他的名字叫..."
His name is..."
埃利奥特
Elliot.
没错
Yeah.
"他要和家人进行一场冒险
"He is going on an adventure with his family.
他们要在森林里野营
They are going camping in the forest.
埃利奥特有..."
Elliot has..."
等等
Wait.
这和我给它念的不一样
This isn't how I tell it.
你要我别念了吗
Would you like me to stop?
不
No.
我喜欢这个故事
I like it.
"埃利奥特从没这么兴奋过
"Elliot has never been so excited.
当妈妈和爸爸在扎帐篷时
Elliot and his boy play,
埃利奥特和他的小伙伴在玩
while Mom and Dad set up the tent.
他就属于这里
He is right where he belongs."
你在找什么吗
You looking for something?
你吓到我了
Oh. You scared me.
你为什么不睡觉
Why aren't you asleep?
你不也没睡 一个原因吧
The same reason you're not, I suppose.
你应该听说了那个男孩
I guess you heard about the boy.
没错
I did.
这个小镇 流言传得很快
You know, word travels fast in this town.
他在森林里待了多久
How long has he been out there?
六年
Six years.
Six years?
没人能在森林里活六年
Nobody can survive in that forest for six years.
至少一个人不行
At least not alone.
他说...
Well... He says...
他说他不是一个人
He says he wasn't alone.
他画的
He drew this?
他说这是森林里的一个朋友
He says it's his friend from the forest.
这让我想起了...
And it reminded me of...
我知道让你想起了什么
I know what it reminded you of.
那个吗
That one?
我几岁的时候 你画的来着
How old was I when you drew this for me?
也许五六岁吧
Uh, maybe five or six.
在你妈去世之前
Just before your mother passed away.
我记得 你认真听我说的每句话
I remember then, you hung on every word I ever said.
总是有很多疑问
You were so full of questions.
爸爸
Dad.
嗯
Hmm?
你在森林里到底看见了什么
What did you really see out there?
拜托 别编另一个故事
Please, don't tell me another story.
就告诉我你记得什么
Just tell me what you remember.
我记得什么
What I remember?
我记得 我当时在打猎...
What I remember is, I was out hunting...
阳光照下来...
and the sun was shining down...
风穿过森林
and wind was blowing through the trees.
我在想"孩子 你就属于这里"
And I remember thinking, "Boy, this is exactly where I belong."
我停在小溪旁喝水
I stopped by a creek to get a drink.
突然间 我发现阳光消失了
Suddenly I realize I wasn't in the sun anymore...
我抬头看什么挡住了天空
and I looked up to see what was blocking the sky.
我怎么只看见了一只龙
And what did I see but a dragon?
我真的看见了一只龙
I see a dragon.
我一辈子都没那么害怕过
I've never been so scared in my life.
但当我举起枪 要开枪...
But when I raised my gun to shoot...
突然有一种感觉...
suddenly there was this feeling, this...
就像魔法一样
It was like magic.
没有其他词能形容它 就是魔法
There's no other word to express it. It was magic.
于是我放下枪 坐在那...
So, I put my gun down and just sat there...
我们隔着小溪 坐在那彼此对视
and we sat there across the creek from each other just looking.
我就坐在那看着
I just sat there looking.
然后龙转身消失在森林里
And then the dragon turned and disappeared into the woods.
我记得当时想"我太幸运了"
And I remember thinking, "I am one lucky guy."
当然 没人相信我
Of course, nobody believed me.
我知道人们怎么谈论我的
I knew what people were saying about me.
我必须承认
I must admit, there were
有一段时间我在想"也许他们是对的"
times when I thought, "Maybe they're right."
但我想到那魔法
But then I thought about the magic.
它改变了我对世界的认识...
It changed the way I see the world...
我对树的认识 对阳光的认识...
the way I see trees, the way I see sunshine...
甚至对你的认识
the way, even, I see you.
我不会和任何东西交换
I wouldn't trade that for anything.
所以我不会尝试说服你 我放弃
So, I'm not gonna try to convince you. I quit that.
但也许你愿意用开放的眼光去看待
But maybe if you could just be open to looking.
我了解那片森林
I know those woods.
我对那片森林了如指掌
I know those woods like the back of my hand.
我不可能错过一只龙
I couldn't have missed a dragon.
可你错过了彼得
Well, you missed Pete.
彼得
Pete.
醒醒 亲爱的
Wake up, honey.
早上好
Good morning.
- 你准备好走了吗 - 没错
- You heading out already? - Yup.
一大早的
Bright and early.
我要去工厂一趟
I'm gonna head over to the mill.
和嘉文聊聊
Talk to Gavin about something.
有需要给我打电话
Call me if you need anything.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
确定吗
You sure?
当然
Absolutely.
# 昨天 你让昨天那么美好 #
Yesterday, Any way you made it was just fine
# 所以你把白天变成昼夜 #
So you'd turn your days into nighttime
# 你不知道 #
Didn't you know
# 你不费力就能成功 #
You can make it without ever even trying
# 你脑中有些想法 #
And something's on your mind
# 对吗 #
Isn't it?
怎么了
What's wrong?
没什么
Nothing.
没什么 我准备调头
Nothing, I just got turned around.
嘿 彼得...
Hey, Pete...
我在想 也许我们能叫个人一起去
I was thinking maybe we could bring someone with us.
一个也认识埃利奥特的人
Someone who might know Elliot, too.
可以吗
Is that okay?
# 你脑中有些想法 #
And something's on your mind
# 对吗 #
Isn't it?
# 也许改日 你会感觉不同 #
Maybe another day, You wanna feel another way
# 你情不自禁地哭泣 #
You can't stop crying
- 嘿 杰克 - 早上好
- Hey, Jack. - Morning.
嘿 杰克
Hey, Jack.
嘿 卡尔文 看见嘉文了吗
Hey, Calvin. You seen Gavin?
他和伍德罗开着卡车
Uh, he and Woodrow took a truck
去新的砍伐点了...
out to the new cut down...
还带了一些人
with some of the other boys.
干嘛
What for?
要猎杀什么
Something about going hunting.
- 打猎 - 我不知道
- Hunting? - I don't know.
打猎
Hunting?
- 杰克·马格里 - 嘿 杰克
- Jack Magary. - Hey, Jack.
你不是说 杰克·马格里带彼得过来了吗
Didn't you say Grace was planning on bringing Pete by?
没错 她一个小时出发的
Yeah, she left an hour ago.
她还没出现
She hasn't shown up yet.
我们找了些人在这干等着
We've got these people standing here.
不知道该做什么
Uh, don't quite know what to do.
好的 谢谢你 警长 我有点事
Uh, okay, thank you, Sheriff. I gotta go.
# 你脑中有些想法 #
Something's on your mind
# 对吗 #
Isn't it?
# 你脑中有些想法 #
Something's on your mind
这边
This way!
# 说实话吧 你脑中有些想法 #
Oh, tell the truth now, Something's on your mind
孩子们 等等
Kids, hold on a second.
# 你脑中有些想法 #
Something's on your mind
埃利奥特
Elliot!
我从没来过森林的这片区域
I've never seen this part of the forest before.
过来
Come on!
太棒了
Cool.
你是怎么靠自己做成这样的
How did you do this by yourself?
埃利奥特帮忙的 我觉得他藏起来了
Elliot helped. I think he's hiding.
埃利奥特
Elliot?
不 彼得 等等...
Oh, no, Pete, wait...
- 我要去找他 - 格蕾丝 等等
- I'm going in after him. - Grace, wait.
给它点时间
Give it a minute.
格蕾丝
Grace?
爸爸
Dad.
过来
Come on.
我跟你说什么来着 魔法
What did I tell you? Magic.
埃利奥特
Elliot.
我跟你说什么来着
What did I tell you?
我抓到他了
I got him!
- 嘉文 - 格蕾丝
- Gavin? - Grace?
- 不不 等等 - 住手
- No! No, wait! - Stop!
把孩子带走
Get those kids outta here!
别杀他 只用麻醉枪
Don't kill him! Tranqs only!
嘉文 你在干嘛
Gavin, what are you doing?
他不危险
He's not dangerous!
他不会伤害... 住手
He's not gonna hurt... Stop!
- 我抓到他了 - 不
- I got him! - No!
- 不 - 住手
- No! - Stop!
埃利奥特
Elliot!
开始 快 起来
Here we go! Come on, get up!
不
No!
博比 开枪
Bobby, take the shot!
住手 埃利奥特
Stop! Elliot!
飞
Fly!
拜托
Come on!
拜托 走 走
Come on! Go! Go!
埃利奥特
Elliot.
小心
Watch out!
那是什么
What is that?
爸爸
Daddy?
娜塔莉
Natalie?
嘉文 那是什么
Gavin, what is this?
这是米尔黑文之龙
This is the Millhaven dragon.
我刚刚抓住它了
And I just caught it.
怎么了 小子们
What's the matter, boys?
你们以前没见过龙吗
Ain't you ever seen a dragon before?
过来
Come on.
把它拉进仓库 进仓库
Pull it into the warehouse. Into the warehouse.
小心 伙计们 小心
Check it out, boys. Check it out!
彼得 格蕾丝也不想这样
Pete, Grace didn't mean for this to happen.
她是个美女 对吧
She's a beauty, isn't she?
还是帅哥 还是它 管他呢
Or he? It? Whatever it is.
相信我 尽快过来
Just trust me. Get here as quick as you can.
娜塔莉
Natalie...
我需要你在这里和彼得等一会儿 好吗
I need you to wait here with Pete for a minute, okay?
埃利奥特会怎么样
What's going to happen to Elliot?
我不知道
I don't know,
但我会想办法的 好吗
but I'm going to go find out, okay?
你们就待在这
I just need you to stay here.
好吗 你们能在这里等我吗
Okay? Will you stay here for me?
- 好的 - 谢谢 亲爱的
- Okay. - Thank you, sweetie.
彼得 我们会搞定的
Pete, we'll fix this.
我发誓
I promise.
好吧 你抓住它了
Okay, then. Now you've caught it.
打算怎么办
What do you plan to do with it?
- 我要怎么对它吗 - 没错
- What am I going to do with it? - Yeah.
我知道要怎么对它
I know exactly what I'm going to do with it.
你根本不知道 对吧
You don't have a clue, do you?
好吧 听着 我还完全没有想好
Okay, look. I haven't got it totally figured out yet.
但我跟你说
But I'll tell you this much.
这件事会让我一举成名
This thing is gonna put me on the map.
人们会不远万里来看它
Folks will come from miles to see this.
- 嘉文 - 杰克能拥有这个工厂
- Gavin. - Jack can have the mill.
龙是我的
The dragon is mine.
不不不 住手
No, no, no! Stop. Stop.
他们在对他做什么
What are they doing to him?
他们正在搞清楚
They're trying to find out
他是什么 他来自哪里
what he is and where he came from.
为什么之前没见过他
And why they've never seen him before.
你在做什么
Hey, what are you doing?
把那些枪拿开
Get those guns out of here.
就像我说的 他来自森林
He came from the woods, just like I did.
你认真的吗
Are you serious?
为什么不能放我们走
Why can't they just let us go?
我们会离开 再也不见任何人
We'll go away. We'll never see anybody again.
就像从前一样
It'll be just like it used to be.
但我不想再也见不到你
But I don't wanna never see you again.
你疯了吗
Are you insane?
你不知道这家伙有什么能力
You have no idea what this thing is capable of.
- 你又知道 - 没错
- And you do? - Yeah.
如果他醒了
If he wakes up,
他会毁了这个小镇 所有人都要搭进去
he could take out the whole town and everyone in it.
杰克 他是个怪兽
Jack, he's a monster.
这不是怪兽 只是个动物
It's not a monster. It's an animal.
而且还受伤了 很害怕
And it's hurt and it's scared.
格蕾丝 等等
Grace, wait.
你需要帮助
You need help.
你需要彼得
You need Pete.
你们看到了吗
Did you see that?
Did you just see that?
看到了
I sure did.
我们走
Let's go.
在天上
Up there.
伙计们 走 警长
Guys, move. Sheriff!
- 警长 警长 - 杰克
- Sheriff! Sheriff! - Jack.
不 走开 退后 警长
No, out of the way. Back off. Sheriff!
走开 警长
Out of the way! Sheriff!
谢谢你来了
Thanks for coming.
杰克 什么情况
Jack, what's so big
得调动整个部队
I had to call out the cavalry?
你真的得进来看看
You really have to come inside and see this.
- 嘉文 - 让我先提醒你
- Gavin. - Let me just say one thing first here.
我兄弟给你打电话是为了...
What my brother called you about...
它属于我 好吗
it belongs to me, okay?
我光明正大地抓到的
I caught it fair and square.
所以 如果有人有什么意见 也该我说
So, if anyone tries to tell you any different, it's mine.
它属于我
It belongs to me.
我想看看
I wanna see!
我们为什么要站在外面
Why are we standing outside?
我们能进去看看嘛
Can we go in and take a look at it?
埃利奥特 你没事吧
Elliot, are you okay?
里面发生了什么
What's going on in there?
我要警告你
Now, I gotta warn you.
这玩意很危险
This thing is dangerous.
我和我的人才知道怎么对付它
Me and my crew are the only ones who know how to deal with it.
所以 一旦我们进去了 保持冷静
So, when you get in there, just stay calm.
别一惊一乍
Don't startle it.
别让人在我眼皮底下被吃了
Don't want anyone getting eaten on my watch.
嘉文 等等
Gavin, wait.
听着 格蕾丝
Listen, Grace,
我们不在森林了 所以里面的东西...
we're not in the forest anymore, so what's in there...
你们可以坐在外面...
You can sit out here...
然后争论"里面有什么"
and talk about "What's in there"
直到双方都气得要死
until you're blue in the face.
我就想看看 都让开
I just want to see it. Now step aside.
我们到这边等 过来
We're waiting over here. Come on.
推开门
Push it open.
怎么回事
What's the deal here?
抱歉 警长
Excuse me, Sheriff.
似乎卡住了
Seems to be stuck.
好吧 拜托 谁在里面
Okay, come on. Who's in there?
嘿 开门
Hey, open up.
埃利奥特
Elliot.
你能飞吗
Can you fly?
再用点力
Hit it harder!
什么都没有
I don't see anything.
- 刚刚还在那 - 什么在这里
- It was right here. - What was right here?
它跑出去了
It got out.
快 我们要找到它 让一让
Come on, we gotta find it! Make a hole!
什么出去了
What got out?
你得亲眼看看 快来
You gotta see for yourself. Come on.
爱博纳 检查院子
Abner, check the yard.
伍德罗 去南边看看
Woodrow, take the South side.
警长 能让你的人分散吗
Sheriff, can you get your men to spread out?
我们需要叫一架直升机 因为龙能飞
We need to call in a chopper, because this dragon can fly.
龙
A dragon?
杰克 你把我叫过来就为了一只龙
Jack, you dragged me all the way out here for a dragon?
我不知道怎么解释 但他说的是真的
I don't know how to explain it, but he's telling the truth.
刚刚还在这
It was here.
它还在那
It's still in there.
- 什么 - 那只龙
- What? - The dragon.
那只龙还在那 我们得帮帮他们
The dragon is still in there. We have to help them.
我们怎么把他弄出去
How do we get him out of here?
你知道怎么开车吗
Do you know how to drive?
大概吧
Sort of,
但我爸爸的卡车可没这么多按钮
but my dad's truck doesn't have this many buttons.
住手 小姑娘
Stop what you're doing, young lady.
你都够不着踏板 挪过去
Your feet don't even reach the pedals. Scoot over.
等等
Wait!
我不想伤害你的朋友 孩子
I don't want to hurt your friend, son.
我只想帮忙
I just want to help.
上来吧
Get in.
好吧 我们看看有没有...
Okay, let's see here if this...
嘿 老朋友
Hey, old buddy.
你们最好系上安全带
You better buckle up.
抓紧了
Hold on tight!
我还以为弄反了
I thought I put it in reverse.
天哪...
Oh, my...
那不是真的吧
That isn't real, is it?
跟着那只龙
Follow that dragon!
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
抱歉
Sorry about that.
告诉那只龙坚持住 我们有客人了
Tell that dragon to hang on. We've got company.
所有分队注意
Attention all units.
我们在米尔黑文路向东行驶 追捕一只...
We're eastbound on Millhaven Road in pursuit of a...
一只龙 一只龙
A dragon! It's a dragon!
你不能在无线电里说龙
You can't say dragon over the radio.
埃利奥特
Elliot!
飞
Fly!
快点
Come on.
再快点
Faster!
那是米查姆
That's Meacham!
靠边停
Pull over!
Hey, pull over!
没门
Not a chance!
那是我的龙
That's my dragon!
他没有减速
He's not slowing down.
他不打算停
He's not stopping.
他会停的
He'll stop.
那蠢货疯了
That fool's out of his mind.
- 停车 - 我在停
- Stop! - I'm trying.
他没那么疯吧
He ain't that crazy.
好吧 坐稳了
Okay, hang on tight.
我们得换个法子了
We're going to have to do this another way.
埃利奥特 不
Elliot! No!
嘿
Hey!
埃利奥特 不
Elliot! No!
杰克
Jack.
住手
Stop!
你必须住手
You have to stop!
杰克
Jack!
他们不会伤害我们的 拜托
They're not gonna hurt us. Please!
住手 埃利奥特 住手
Stop! Elliot, stop!
被伤害他们 我需要他们
Don't hurt them! I need them!
我需要他们
I need them.
杰克 快出来
Jack, get out of there!
- 嘉文 - 打碎玻璃
- Gavin? - Break the glass!
快啊 我抓着
Come on, I got ya!
拜托 埃利奥特
Come on, Elliot!
- 爸爸 - 飞
- Daddy! - Fly!
我们走 快
Let's go. Go!
过来
Come on!
爸爸
Daddy!
不 格蕾丝...
No, Grace...
拜托 埃利奥特
Come on, Elliot.
拜托
Come on.
格蕾丝
Grace.
我知道
I know.
彼得
Pete.
彼得 等等
Pete! Wait!
我们不能再留在这了
We can't stay here anymore.
人们知道你在这里 他们会来找你
People know you're here. They'll come looking for you.
但我不能隐身
But I can't disappear.
但我也不想离开你
But I don't want to leave you.
亲爱的 看啊
Honey, look.
再也没人见过那只龙
No one ever saw that dragon again.
我也没讲过关于它的其他传说
And I never told another tale about it.
那天之后 也不必说了
I didn't have to. Not after that day.
人们四处寻找
Folks looked high and low,
但都徒劳无功
but it was nowhere to be found.
有人说他飞去了其他的森林
Some said he flew to another forest
很远很远
far, far away.
但那些只是故事
But those were just stories.
时光飞逝
Time marched on.
孩子长大
Children got older.
树木茁壮 故事也变长
Trees growed taller. Tales growed taller, too.
最好的故事也会结束
By and by, even the best ones come to an end.
但我知道有人 会告诉你其他事
But I know someone who would tell you otherwise.
有一个小男孩
There's one little boy
能告诉你整个故事
who could tell you the whole story.
他能告诉你 接下来发生了什么
He could even tell you what happens next.
他知道北极星是夜空中最亮的星
He knows that the North Star shines brightest of all.
他知道森林里有魔法
He knows that there's magic in the woods,
如果你知道在哪的话
if you know where to look for it.
他知道他的龙还在那里
He knows his dragon is still out there.
也许 如果你走运...
Maybe, if you're lucky...
同一个男孩...
that same boy...
我见过最勇敢的男孩...
the bravest boy I've ever met...
他能告诉你哪里能找到他
he could tell you where to find him.
# 你为自己画下蓝图 #
You had your maps drawn
# 你心中已有盘算 只为仅有的希望 #
You had other plans to hang your hopes on
# 每条路都让你绝望 怀疑自己的选择  #
Every road they led you down, Felt so wrong
# 所以你为自己发掘新的路 #
So you found another way
# 你宽阔的胸怀 #
You've got a big heart
# 让你审视整个世界 让你坚持那么久 #
The way you see the world, It got you this far
# 或许你会伤痕累累 或许会遍体鳞伤 #
You might have some bruises and a few scars
# 但你知道你终究会安然无恙 #
But you know you're gonna be okay
# 即便你恐惧害怕 #
And even though you're scared
# 你仍是最坚强的那个 #
You're stronger than you know
# 如果你迷失于没有一丝光亮的黑暗 #
If you're lost out where the lights are blinding
# 置身于没有一丝星光的黑夜 #
Caught and all the stars are hiding
# 那时 原野的呼唤会指引你回家的路 #
That's when something wild calls you home
# 家 #
Home
# 如果恐惧让你徘徊原地 #
If you face the fear that keeps you frozen
# 投身无边汪洋追逐远方 #
Chase the sky into the ocean
# 那时 原野的呼唤会指引你回家的路 #
That's when something wild calls you home
# 家 #
Home
# 呼唤你回家 #
Calls you home
# 如果你迷失于没有一丝光亮的黑暗 #
You're lost out where the lights are blinding
# 置身于没有一丝星光的黑夜 #
Caught and all the stars are hiding
# 那时 原野的呼唤会指引你回家的路 #
That's when something wild calls you home
# 如果你迷失于没有一丝光亮的黑暗 #
If you're lost out where the lights are blinding
# 置身于没有一丝星光的黑夜 #
Caught and all the stars are hiding
# 那时 原野的呼唤会指引你回家的路 #
That's when something wild calls you home
# 家 #
Home
# 如果恐惧让你停滞原地 #
If you face the fear that keeps you frozen
# 投身无边汪洋追逐远方 #
Chase the sky into the ocean
# 那时 原野的呼唤会指引你回家的路 #
That's when something wild calls you home
# 家 #
Home
# 去北方 去北方 #
Go North, go North
# 用你脚上的翅膀去北方 #
With wings on your feet
# 乘着风去北方 #
Go North with the wind
# 那里有三条交汇的河 #
Where the three rivers meet
# 在树林之中 #
There's a clearing of sorts
# 有一块空地 #
In the circle of trees
# 野外的天空闪烁星座点点 #
Where the wild constellations shine One two and three
# 看看你的周围 #
Look all around you and see
# 森林的深处有古龙 #
Deep in the forest there dragons will be
# 他们生于地球 #
They come from the Earth
# 没错 他们生于石头 #
Yes, they come from the stone
# 寒冷的北方 #
The icy, cold North
# 那是他们的家 #
That's where they call home
# 去山海交界处 #
Go where the mountain kisses the sea
# 用该一点 比我勇敢一点 #
Better be brave, Far braver than me
# 看看你的周围 #
Look all around you and see
# 森林的深处有古龙 #
Deep in the forest there dragons will be
# 如果龙找到了你 #
If a dragon should find you
# 你应该快跑 #
You might ought to run
# 没人经历过这样的争论 #
No one has lived through such a run-in, not one
# 如果你听见了咆哮 #
So if you hear a roar
# 天哪 快离远点 #
Goodness sake, leave them be
# 你在天上找到他们 #
Up where you find them
# 自由自在 #
Wild and free
# 看看你的周围 #
Look all around you and see
# 森林的深处有古龙 #
Deep in the forest there dragons will be
# 看看你的周围 #
Look all around you
# 你就会找到我 #
You won't find me
支持我们，欢迎购买VIP移除所有广告，具体：www.OpenSubtitles.org